<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Human Body Organ</string>
    <string name="parts_of_the_body">PARTS OF THE BODY</string>
    <string name="click_here">Click Here</string>


    <string name="arm">Arm</string>
    <string name="ear">Ear</string>
    <string name="elbow">Elbow</string>
    <string name="foot">Foot</string>
    <string name="hand_wrist">Hand Wrist</string>
    <string name="hip">Hip</string>
    <string name="knuckle">Knuckle</string>
    <string name="middle_finger">Middle Finger</string>
    <string name="palm">Palm</string>
    <string name="picky_finger">Picky Finger</string>
    <string name="pointer_finger">Pointer Finger</string>
    <string name="ring_finger">Ring Finger</string>
    <string name="teeth">Teeth</string>
    <string name="thumb">Thumb</string>


    <!--    New One-->

    <string name="face">Face</string>
    <string name="scalp">Scalp</string>
    <string name="forehead">Forehead</string>
    <string name="mouth">Mouth</string>
    <string name="eyes">Eyes</string>
    <string name="eyelid">Eyelid</string>
    <string name="eyelash">Eyelash</string>
    <string name="jaw">Jaw</string>
    <string name="upper_arm">Upper arm</string>
    <string name="forearm">Forearm</string>
    <string name="fingernail">Fingernail</string>
    <string name="shin">Shin</string>
    <string name="ankle">Ankle</string>
    <string name="heel">Heel</string>
    <string name="torso">Torso</string>
    <string name="abdomen">Abdomen</string>
    <string name="belly_button">Belly Button</string>
    <string name="buttock">Buttock</string>


    <!--    new Description-->

    <string name="face_desc">Face is front of the head, use for five senses; communicating emotions</string>
    <string name="scalp_desc">Scalp is top of the head (under hair), for cooling the head with
        sweat glands in the skin; protecting the skull with extra blood vessels</string>
    <string name="forehead_desc">Forehead is top of the face, above the eyes, for forming
        facial expressions; protecting the eyes</string>
    <string name="mouth_desc">Mouth is below the nose, for eating; talking; breathing; sense of taste</string>
    <string name="eyes_desc">Eyes is below the forehead, above the nose, use for sense of sight</string>
    <string name="eyelid_desc">Eyelid is just above the eye, protecting the eyes from
        foreign particles; enable eyes to close</string>
    <string name="eyelash_desc">Eyelash is on the edges of the eyelid, protecting the eyes from foreign particles</string>
    <string name="jaw_desc">Jaw is on top of the mouth (maxilla) and bottom of the mouth (mandible)
        , chewing; opening and closing the mouth; talking</string>
    <string name="upper_arm_desc">Upper arm is between shoulders and elbows, flexing the arm;
        connecting the lower arm to the shoulder</string>
    <string name="forearm_desc">Forearm is between elbows and wrists, flexing the wrist;
        connecting the arm to the wrist</string>
    <string name="fingernail_desc">Fingernail is end of finger, protecting nail beds from foreign
        particles; helping with grip</string>
    <string name="shin_desc">Shin is lower leg, under the knee, flexing the foot; stabilizing
        the ankle</string>
    <string name="ankle_desc">Ankle is joint between the foot and shin, rotating the foot;
        connecting the foot to the leg</string>
    <string name="heel_desc">Heel is back of the foot, distributing body weight</string>
    <string name="torso_desc">Torso is middle of the body, between the neck and legs, stabilizing
        the body (posture); protecting internal organs; connecting the limbs (arms and legs) to the body</string>
    <string name="abdomen_desc">Abdomen is middle of the torso, stabilizing the body; protecting internal organs</string>
    <string name="belly_button_desc">Belly Button is the middle of the belly, connects a
        baby’s umbilical cord to its mother’s placenta before birth</string>
    <string name="buttock_desc">Buttock is back of the torso, just above the legs, cushioning
        the body when sitting; assisting in hip and thigh movement</string>


    <!--  Description  -->
    <string name="arm_desc">Arm is a human upper limb especially the part between
        the shoulder and the wrist. something like or corresponding to an arm.
        such as the forelimb of a vertebrate.</string>
    <string name="ear_desc">Ear is on either side of the head, sense of hearing; maintaining balance</string>
    <string name="elbow_desc">Elbow is joint between the upper arm and forearm, connecting the
        upper arm to the forearm; extending the arm; rotating the lower arm</string>

    <string name="foot_desc">The foot is an anatomical structure found in many vertebrates.
        It is the terminal portion of a limb which bears weight and allows locomotion. </string>

    <string name="hand_wrist_desc">Wrist is the part of the body between
        hand and arm which bends when you move your hand.</string>
    <string name="hip_desc">Hips are the two areas at the sides of your body
        between the tops of your legs and your waist.</string>
    <string name="knuckle_desc">Knuckle is the joint between hand bones (carpals) and finger bones
        (phalanges) connecting the fingers to the hand; allow fingers to bend and extend</string>

    <string name="middle_finger_desc">Middle finger commonly referred to as the long or
        tall finger sits in the center of the hand. </string>

    <string name="palm_desc">Palm is flat side of hand, helping with grip; sense of touch</string>

    <string name="picky_finger_desc">Picky finger is the fifth digit and smallest of the fingers.</string>

    <string name="pointer_finger_desc">The index finger is the second digit of the hand. Along with
        the thumb and middle finger, it is one of the most often-used digits. This finger has practical applications of both sensory touch and grasp, but it is often used for expressive purposes as well. This usually takes the form of non-verbal hand gestures. For this reason, the index finger is also known as ‘the pointer’. </string>
    <string name="ring_finger_desc">The ring finger refers to the fourth digit of each hand,
        located between the middle and pinky fingers.</string>

    <string name="teeth_desc">Tooth, plural teeth, any of the hard,
        resistant structures occurring on the jaws and in or around
        the mouth and pharynx areas of vertebrates. Teeth are used for
        catching and masticating food, for defense, and for other
        specialized purposes.</string>

    <string name="thumb_desc">the short thick digit of the human hand that is
        analogous in position to the big toe and differs from the other fingers
        in having only two phalanges, allowing greater freedom of movement, and
        being opposable to each of them also, Different from the other four digits
        in that it is shorter and wider and only has two phalanges instead of three,
        the thumb earned its name from a description of its physical characteristics
        in relation to its neighbors. </string>

    <string name="hair">Hair</string>
    <string name="head">Head</string>
    <string name="neck">Neck</string>
    <string name="chest">Chest</string>
    <string name="shoulder">Shoulder</string>
    <string name="stomach">Stomach</string>
    <string name="wrist">Wrist</string>
    <string name="hand">Hand</string>
    <string name="finger">Finger</string>
    <string name="thigh">Thigh</string>
    <string name="knee">Knee</string>
    <string name="skin">Skin</string>
    <string name="leg">Leg</string>
    <string name="toe">Toe</string>

    <!--    Description-->

    <string name="hair_desc">Hair is on top of the scalp, regulating body temperature;
        protecting the scalp</string>
    <string name="head_desc">The human head is home to all the body\'s major sensory organs, and
        the most important of these is the brain. Although the nose, ears, tongue, nerves, and others parts are important, without a healthy brain, they\'d all be useless. Encased in the skull, the brain is the body\'s centralized conveyor of all information.</string>
    <string name="neck_desc">Neck is below the head, above the shoulders, for supporting the head’s
        weight; allowing the head to turn; sending messages from the brain to the rest of the body (vertebrae)</string>
    <string name="chest_desc">Chest is top of the torso, protecting lungs and heart;
        assisting in arm movement</string>
    <string name="shoulder_desc">The shoulder is one of the largest and most complex joints in the
        body. The shoulder joint is formed where the humerus (upper arm bone) fits into the scapula (shoulder blade), like a ball and socket. Other important bones in the shoulder include: The acromion is a bony projection off the scapula.</string>
    <string name="stomach_desc">Stomach</string>
    <string name="wrist_desc">The wrist connects the hand to the forearm. It consists of the distal
        ends of the radius and ulna bones, eight carpal bones, and the proximal ends of five metacarpal bones. This arrangement of bones allows for a wide range of movement. The wrist can bend, straighten, move laterally, and rotate.</string>

    <string name="hand_desc">hand is end of the arm, connected to the wrist,
        fine motor skills (writing, pinching, gripping) </string>
    <string name="finger_desc">finger is end of hand, helping with grip;
        sense of touch; gesturing (pointing, hand signals, etc.)</string>
    <string name="thigh_desc">Thigh is top of leg, above the knee, allowing the leg to flex and
        move; supporting weight of the upper body</string>
    <string name="knee_desc">Knee is joint between the thigh and shin, bending the leg;
        supporting weight of the upper body</string>
    <string name="skin_desc">Skin</string>
    <string name="leg_desc">Legs are below torso, above foot, keeping the body stable; walking;
        running; bending the body</string>
    <string name="toe_desc">Toe is end of the foot, providing balance while walking;
        distributing body weight</string>


    <string name="your_search_will_be_displayed_here">Your search will be displayed here</string>
    <string name="change_language">Change Language</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="exit_title">Are you sure you want to exit?</string>
    <string name="yes">YES</string>
    <string name="no">NO</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="search_body">Search Body</string>
    <string name="no_search_found">No Search Found</string>
    <string name="image">Image</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="welcome_text">DEVELOPMENT OF AN ANDROID BASED MULTILINGUAL HUMAN BODY ORGAN TUTORING SYSTEM</string>
    <string name="please_wait">please wait...</string>
</resources>